

# Gökalp Giray

## Frontend Developer

**★** gokalpgiray.github.io/Portfolio/ **in** gokalpgiray **()** GokalpGiray

### **₽** Profile

Hello. I wanted to embody my interest in software development, which has started in the last years of my university life, and turn it into my profession. I have chosen frontend development as a new career path for myself. For this purpose, I am still working hard. Using the work ethic and discipline I've gained from my work experience for many years, I am trying to become an expert in this field by constantly improving myself. You can check my work on my GitHub page.

### **Education**

2015 – 2020	Bachelor's Degree, Survey Engineering, Çanakkale Onsekiz Mart University ∂	Çanakkale, Turkey
2014 – 2015	English Preparation, School of Foreign Languages, Karadeniz Technical University ⊘	Trabzon, Turkey
2010 – 2014	<b>High School, Math - Science,</b> Fahreddin Kerim Gökay Anatolian High School	İstanbul, Turkey

# Professional Experience

	•	
07/2021 - 09/2022	<b>Survey Engineer,</b> 3408/22 No'lu Lisanslı Harita Kadastro Mühendislik Bürosu	Istanbul, Turkey
02/2020 - 07/2021	<b>Quality Control Specialist,</b> <i>GKN Sinter İstanbul Metal San. ve Tic.A.Ş.</i>	Istanbul, Turkey
07/2019 - 01/2020	Travel Consultant, Capacity Jolly Tur	Istanbul, Turkey
12/2018 - 03/2019	<b>Intern Survey Engineer,</b> 1706/98 No'lu Lisanslı Harita Kadastro Mühendislik Bürosu	Çanakkale, Turkey
07/2017 - 09/2017	Intern Survey Engineer, Küçükçekmece Kadastro Birimi	Istanbul, Turkey

## 🗁 Projects

#### gurmesef1974.com ∂

The website I prepared for Gurme Şef 1974

## **®** Skills

React

- JavaScript
- HTML

• CSS

- Bootstrap
- Redux

Matlab

**Turkish** 

• git

Java

• MS Office

# **&** Languages

# English

Intermediate Native Language

## **Certificates**

Beginner Frontend Web Development Path ∂

HTML5 and CSS3 Fundamentals ∂

Intermediate Frontend Web Development Path  $\mathscr D$ 

## $\sqrt{\phantom{a}}$ Familiar With

### **Agile**

Scrum and Kanban

## ⁄ d Interests

#### **Basketball**

I have been watching, playing, listening and following basketball for many years. Even though I can't watch the matches all the time, I somehow follow the leagues.

#### Formula 1

Especially in recent years, my interest in Formula 1, which I watched as a child, has flared up again. I try to follow it as closely as possible. Forza Ferrari!

#### **Tennis**

I've been watching and playing since I was a kid. This sport taught me to manage my ambition and patience.

## **ಿ** References

**Oğuz Özkeroğlu**, *Senior Software Engineer*, Ericsson Sweden oguz.ozkeroglu@ericsson.com, +46 72 300 50 80

**Serhat Akkuş**, *Software Lead* serhatakkus@gmail.com, +90 535 610 64 33

**Melek Pazarbaşı**, *Software Engineer*, ING Türkiye melekp30@gmail.com, +90 538 979 22 90

**Taha Furkan Tarakçı**, *Frontend Web Developer*, Figopara tahatarakci34@gmail.com, +90 535 255 61 47